http://www.hotshotproducts.com/privacy-policy.html

2016 marked Miller's 75th anniversary. Learn More >
NEW PRODUCT:
Plastic Poultry Feeders and Waterers From Poultry Feeders and Waterers to Maple Sugaring Supplies, learn about our new products here.
Explore Products >
TOOLS FOR OUR TEAM:
Product FAQs Find out the answers to common questions about Miller products!Find Resources >
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Miller Manufacturing values our customers and we respect your privacy. We do collect customer information in an effort to provide the best shopping experience and to communicate with our customers about our promotions, sweepstakes, contests and products. We limit the information collected to what is needed to conduct business and offer products and services that might be of interest to you. Your personal information will not be used for any purpose other than those described above, unless required by law or legal process. Information Sharing Miller Manufacturing does not sell or rent your name or personal information for use by any outside company or third party. We may use customer information for our own marketing and promotional purposes. Miller Manufacturing does contract with third parties to help us maintain and manage our customer information to enable us to communicate with you our customers. We do not authorize any of those third parties to make any other use of your information. We also may share aggregate, non-personally identifiable information about you (such as your age, gender and types of products purchased) with our business associates to fulfill our contractual obligations. Except as described above, we do not share, rent or sell any information we collect online to any unaffiliated third party.
Hot Offers - Don't Miss Anything!!!
Subscribe
